{
    "subject": "resource/Crusader_(Bloor_novel)",
    "predicate": "ontology/author",
    "object": "resource/Edward_Bloor",
    "human_readable": "The author of 'Crusader' novel is Edward Bloor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9337188005447388,
            "question": "Are there other novels written by Edward Bloor besides 'Crusader'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8718928694725037,
            "question": "Who wrote the novel 'Crusader'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8714594841003418,
            "question": "What novel was written by Edward Bloor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.787246823310852,
            "question": "What is the name of the author of 'Crusader'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6658670902252197,
            "question": "Can you tell me the title of a book by Edward Bloor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5845536589622498,
            "question": "Edward Bloor is known for writing what type of stories?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34746071696281433,
            "question": "Is 'Crusader' a work of fiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.282296746969223,
            "question": "What might be some common themes explored in 'Crusader'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2766072452068329,
            "question": "What genre does the novel 'Crusader' likely fall under?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21965432167053223,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in 'Crusader'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The author of 'Crusader' novel is Edward Bloor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7969_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does the novel 'Crusader' likely fall under?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7969_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be some common themes explored in 'Crusader'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7969_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Crusader' a work of fiction?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7969_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7969_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7969_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7969_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7969_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7969_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7969_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7969_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7969_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7969_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7969_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that \"Crusader\" is a novel written by Edward Bloor. Therefore, the statement \"The author of 'Crusader' novel is Edward Bloor\" is correct according to the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}